>> Jem Young: 因此，让我们创建 SSH 密钥。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So let's create an SSH key.
我们想做的是想把它变成我们的 .ssh 目录
What we wanna do is we wanna
cd into our .ssh directory.
如果你是在一台 Mac 机器上
If you're on a Mac machine,
that's gonna be the default place for
所有 SSH 密钥都存在。
all of your SSH keys live.
我想让你用 ls 命令把那些文件列出来看看里面有什么
I want you to list out those files using
ls command just to see what's in there.
然后我们将运行 ssh-keygen >> Jem Young: 所以我现在就做。
And then we're gonna run ssh-keygen
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So I'll do that now.
那是第一排
That's row one.
>> Jem Young: So my home directory .ssh。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So
cd my home directory .ssh.
现在我在这里
Now I'm in here.
我的钥匙不是什么意思
List of my keys, they don't mean anything.
然后我们要运行 ssh-keygen
And then we're gonna run ssh-keygen.
所以让我澄清一下， ssh-keygen.
So let me just clear that, ssh-keygen.
你的小费和你会用什么时间
Pro tip and
what you will use all the time,
如果你签了就会为你自动完成，真的，真的，
if you tab it will try to autocomplete for
you, which is really, really,
真的很有用而且我想逃跑
really useful and I wanna run keygen.
我可以这样说，我也可以。
So I can say that, and I tab.
>> Jem Young: 它会问我想要保存文件名的内容。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: It's gonna ask me what
I want to save the file name as.
如果你有一个叫 ID_rsan的 SSH 密钥
If you have an SSH key called ID_rsan,
这是缺省名称，请使用其他名称，否则会发生冲突。
which is the default name, use a different
name otherwise it will conflict.
我要用全堆的前端
I'm gonna use full stack front end.
我要用两个你不用用两个
I'm gonna use two,
you don't have to use two.
我已经有一个完整的栈前端密钥了
I already have an original
full stack front end key,
我不记得哪个服务器去了
which I don't remember
which server goes to.
所以我不想把它删掉
So I don't wanna delete it
cuz if I lose my ssh-key,
我被关在自己的服务器上了
I'm locked out of my own server.
所以我会创造一个新的
So I'll create a new one.
如果需要，可以使用口令。
You can use a passphrase if you want.
我不会这么做的但如果你是你的
I won't for this case, but
you generally should if you're
定期使用 ssh 密钥，并将其保留为空白。
using ssh-key regularly, and
it's gonna leave it blank.
它生成了这个随机的关键艺术图像。
And it generated this
random key art image.
所有人都有 SSH 密钥吗
All right, everybody have an SSH key?
>> 扬声器 2: 否，当我尝试使用 cd 命令时，没有这样的文件或目录
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: No, I'm getting on no
such file or directory when I try to cd
- > > Jem Young: 好的，没问题。
the into the-
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Okay, not a problem.
所以我们能做的就是去 cd，其实我就做，
So what we can do is we can go to cd,
actually I'll just do,
我们可以制作目录
we can run make directory.
所以 mkdir -/.ssh ，实际上我要运行 -p，
So mkdir -/.ssh, actually,
I'm gonna run -p,
只要它还不存在就可以了
p just means it will make it
if it doesn't already exist.
现在应该有 SSH 目录。
And you should have an SSH directory now.
所以现在如果我们清楚了，我就会去列出档案。
So now if we clear, so
I'll do ls to list files.
我要用管道运营商来管输出，就是这条棒。
I'm gonna pipe the output using the pipe
operator, which is just this bar.
我要去格雷普所以我要定期
And I'm going to grep, so
I'm gonna run a regular
表达式尝试查找我的密钥，完整堆栈前端 2。
expression to try to find my key,
full stack front end 2.
如果您进行搜索，那么应该有两个文件。
And you should have two
files if you do a search.
当然根据你的档案你的贪欲
And of course, depending on what
you named your file, you grep for
不一样的东西
something different.
但我们有私人钥匙
But here we have the private key.
所以它不会在 .pub 中结束，然后我们就有了公钥。
So it doesn't end in .pub, and
then we have the public key.
我可以给你展示公共钥匙，完整的堆前端 2。
So I can show you that public key,
full stack front end 2.
我不是担心你闯入我的服务器
Not that I'm worried about you
breaking into my server but
你一般都不应该给人看你的私人钥匙
you generally shouldn't show
people your private key.
>> Jem Young: 长串的长串长串
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And It looks like
this long string of gibberish and
这才是关键
that's just the key.
所以我可以和任何人分享这个公钥，我可以把它发邮件给你。
So I can share this public key out
with anybody, I can email it to you.
我要把它放到我的服务器上
I'm gonna end up putting it on my server.
但我可以在任何地方都分享
But I can share it everywhere.
通过使用这个公用密钥，我可以加密我要发送给您的所有数据。
And using this public key, I can
encrypt all the data I wanna send you.
现在，我是唯一一个使用此专用密钥来解密数据的人。
And I am the only one now using this
private key that can decrypt that data.
这是一个很神奇的概念。
It's a really amazing concept.
每个人都有类似的产出我们都有钥匙
Everybody have like some sort of output
looks like that, we all have keys,
我猜也是
I'm assuming.
有什么问题吗
Any questions on the commands I used?
好的私人钥匙公用钥匙
Cool, yeah, private key, public key.
这是我喜欢的事我不知道为什么
This is something that I like
honestly I don't know why but
我花了很长时间包围着它
it took me a long time to
wrap my head around it.
也许这不是私人的
Probably cuz it's not .private.
我不知道他们为什么不把它给我私人和酒吧
I don't know why they didn't make
it .private and .pub, I'm like,
哪个才是对的
which one is the right one?
它永远是一个公共的钥匙
It's always gonna be a public key.
绝不会是私人钥匙
Never gonna be a private key.
所以现在我们要登录了
And so now, we're gonna log in.
>> Jem Young: 其实在我们之前
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Actually before we do that,
这整个过程都在给这个数字海洋添加一个 SSH 密钥。
the whole point of this was adding
an SSH key to this Digital Ocean.
记住我们需要那个公用钥匙吗
So remember, we need that public key?
所以我们想做的是你能用
So what we wanna do is you can use,
根据您所开启的操作系统，您可以说 pd 副本。
depending on the operating system
you're on, you can say pd copy.
但我要在这里用鼠标
But I'm just gonna use my mouse here.
别对我说
Don't judge me.
> > Jem Young: 我要把它贴在其中。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And I'm gonna paste that in.
>> Jem Young: 我将它称为全堆栈前端 p2 键。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And I'll just call
it full stack front end p2 key.
如果你再挂的话，这就是我喜欢数字海洋的原因。
And if anytime you get hung up again,
that's why I love Digital Ocean.
他们有一个很好的社区
They have a really good community.
他们有完整的指示信息如何保存和复制您的公共和
They have entire instructions here about
how to save and copy your public and
私人钥匙之类的
private key and things like that.
它们更详细地研究了这些其他的东西。
And they go into more detail and
all these other things.
我们可以接着说，很酷。
And we can just go ahead and
add that, cool.
确保这个被检查过
And make sure this one is checked.
如果您有其他要使用的键，就像在您的
If you have additional keys that you
wanna use, as in they're already on your
计算机，您不想生成新的计算机，也可以单击这些。
computer, you don't wanna generate a new
one, you can just click those as well.
但我现在就用一个
But I'm just gonna use one for now.
>> Jem Young: 当我们向下滚动到我们需要的微滴时
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And when we scroll down
to how many droplets we need, so
微滴就像一个服务器的一小部分
droplets are just like
a fraction of a server.
我可以创造两，三，四，无论我想要什么，但我不会这么做。
I can create two, three, four, whatever
I want, but I'm not gonna do that.
我今天才要创建一个我们不想去处理你的账单
I'm just gonna create one today,
cuz we don't wanna run up your bill.
还有主持人的名字，老实说，这不重要。
And the host name, honestly,
it doesn't matter.
[ LAUGH] 有一个 XKCD 关于命名服务器的笑话，这真的很困难，因为
[LAUGH] There's an XKCD joke about naming
servers, that it's really hard because
服务器将会使用很长的时间，并且无法重命名。
servers will live a very long time and
they're impossible to rename.
不是不可能的但要重命名很难
Well, not impossible but
it's very difficult to rename.
所以如果你想聪明就像堆前堆一样
So if you try to get clever and
like full stack front end,
永远不会死的我不知道
never gonna die server, I don't know.
我不知道我的名字在哪里
I don't know where I'm going
with my naming thing, but
对计算机科学的命名很困难
naming things in computer science is hard.
随便取个名字就不重要了
Just pick a random name,
it doesn't really matter.
我们已经，我可以在 Netflix 上说，因为我们的服务器名称
We have been, I can say at Netflix we've
been burned on our server names because
我们会给它打电话我不知道我们会把它叫做 EC 网络服务器
we'll call it, I don't know,
we'll call it like EC web server one.
如果我们移动到不同的主机，我们就不再是 AWS 中的 EC2 实例了，所以
And if we move to a different host, we're
no longer on EC2 instances from AWS, so
这名字就没道理了
the name doesn't make sense anymore.
那么五年之后，人们就像这样意味着什么 ?
So five years later,
people are like what does this mean?
没人知道我们的名字已经消失了
And then nobody knows anymore
cuz the naming is lost.
命名很困难。
Naming is hard.
完全是正切的
Totally, totally a tangent there.
但没关系
But that's okay.
我们可以制造一个小滴。
And we can create a droplet.
我们不需要备份，因为我们没有做任何重要的事情。
We don't need backups because, well,
we're not doing anything that critical.
但是，总体而言，您要一直备份您的数据。
But, in general,
you wanna back up your data all the time.
Stuff 出错，数据中心发生火灾，黑客入侵。
Stuff goes wrong,
data centers have fires, hackers get in.
你几乎总是想备份你的数据
You almost always wanna back up your data.
但在这件事上我们会没事的
But in this case, we'll be okay.
我要去创造那个小滴
I'm just gonna create that droplet.
>> Jem Young: 它在建筑。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And it's building.
>> 演讲者 3: 您是否启用了备份?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Did you enable backups?
>> Jem Young: 不，除非你真的想
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: No,
not unless you really want to but
这会给你带来更多的钱没有特别的理由
it'll just cost you more money for
no particular reason.
现在它正在建筑中
And now it's building.
> > Jem Young: Cool，我们该起床了
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Cool,
we should be up and running now.
>> Jem Young: 因此，我已为服务器分配了 IP 地址，因此
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So I've been assigned
IP address to my server so
我能联系到它
that I can connect to it.
所以我要去打拷贝
So I'm gonna hit copy.
这里是个很棒的小指令或者你可以只强调
It's a nice little command there or
you can just highlight but
其实是不好的
it actually doesn't work that well.
那就复制吧
So copy that.